杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 让我们继续来稍微修改一下我们的文档页面,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Let's go ahead and
style up our docs page a little bit,
我不想再强调这一点了，这次更新很有用。
I wanna de-emphasize this,
this update time is useful.
但是我们不希望它就在你面前
But we don't want it to be
like right in your face or
看起来和屏幕上的其他内容一样重要。
to look as important as the rest
of the content on the screen.
因此，让我们进入我们的文档页面，让我们添加一些样式，和
So let's go into our docs page,
and let's add some styles, and
我要替换掉反应。
I'm gonna do that by replacing React.
我们要使用 JSX pragma，再次，我要从 theme-ui 导入 JSX。
We're gonna use the JSX pragma, again,
I'm gonna import JSX from theme-ui.
然后我会在这里添加一些基本的样式,
And then I'm going to just
add some basic styles here,
我们做 sx。
we'll do sx.
在它里面，我们可以说边界顶部，现在,
And inside of it,
we can say the border top, and now,
我们要进入一个高级病例。
we're gonna get into an advanced case.
你可以把整个主题对象作为一个道具,
You can actually just access
the whole theme object as a prop,
或者作为一个参数传递给一个函数，所以我可以做主题和
or as an argument passed to a function,
so I can just do theme and
然后把我想要的东西都还给我。
then return whatever I want from it.
所以如果我想设置我的边界
So if I want to set my border for
1px soli，d and
example to be 1px soli,d and
然后我们用主题，色彩，静音，就行了。
then we'll use the theme.colors.muted,
that'll work.
然后我可以将文本本身的颜色设置为静音。
And then I can set the color of
the text itself to be muted.
我可以设置字体大小，我们会使它小一点，所以我会设置为14。
I can set the font size, we'll make it
a little bit smaller so I'll set at 14.
我们需要一些边距顶部，我们需要一些填充顶部，和
We want some margin top,
we want some padding top, and
看看效果如何，看起来不错。
let's see how that looks,
yeah, that looks pretty good.
它不再重要，很明显它是事物的一个单独的部分。
It's de-emphasize, it's clear that
it's a separate part of thing.
它没有占据整个页面，而且
It's not taking over the the page, and
我觉得这个地方可能是个不错的称呼。
that, I think is probably
a good place to call this set.
所以让我们开始工作，然后继续前进。
So let's commit our work,
and then we can move on.
讲者2: 快速提问。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Quick question.
杰森: 是吗 演讲者2: 在第12行,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Yeah?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In the line number 12,
你在那里设置顶部的边界。
where you set the border for
the top there.
杰森: 什么事 扬声器2: 你有没有刚才用过的
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Yes?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Do you have just use
静音的字符串，还是必须使用返回值？
the string muted, or
do you have to use that return?
Jasonlengstorf: 主题 UI 具有设置为接受的特定字段
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Theme UI has certain
fields that are set up to accept
关键字 border top 是一个复合字段，所以它不是。
the keywords, border top is
a composite field, so it doesn't.
这是因为你必须进行一些字符串解析
And that's because you'd have to
get into some string parsing that
可能会很棘手。
could get really tricky.
所以为了防止复杂性,
So as just a guard against complexity,
他们选择使用函数语法代替。
they opted to use
the functions syntax instead.
我相信在主题 UI 站点上有哪些字段的参考
There is on the Theme UI site I
believe a reference of which fields
接受哪些关键词。
accepts which keywords.
然后在其他情况下比如诚实地尝试一下如果不成功,
And then in any other case, like
honestly try it, and if it doesn't work,
切换到功能版本。
just switch out for the function version.
所以让我们把这件事搞定。
So let's get this committed.
添加主题 UI 并将其向上推。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Add Theme UI and
get that pushed up.
好吧
Okay, so